freedomvoice.com 2016-06-29

# Keeping Your Data Safe - Privacy Policy for FreedomVoice.com.

  * Home
  * Privacy Policy

 **Privacy Policy Overview**

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for FreedomVoice.com and the FreedomVoice mobile application and applies solely to information collected by this website and by the mobile application. It will notify you of the following:

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website and mobile application, how it is used, and with whom it may be shared.
  * The security procedures in place to protect against the misuse of your information.
  * Your options regarding the use of your data.
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information collected.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this website or through the app. We only have access to/collect personally identifiable information that you voluntarily give us. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request or in response to a lawful request by law enforcement.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about promotions, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

**Encryption & Security**

We take great precaution to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website or the FreedomVoice mobile application, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information, such as credit card data, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. This applies to information collected on FreedomVoice.com and information collected through the FreedomVoice mobile application.  You can verify this on FreedomVoice.com by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.  For the FreedomVoice mobile application, although it is not possible to confirm it visually, information is only transmitted using HTTPS.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

**Your Access to and Control over Information**

You may opt out of any future contact from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**Placing an Order**

When placing an order through our website, we may request information from you as part of placing an order for service. To start service with us, you must provide contact information, including but not necessarily limited to first and last name, phone number, and email address, as well as financial information including but not necessarily limited to a credit card number, expiration date, and billing address. This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your order. If you experience trouble processing your order for service, we may use this information to contact you to assist you with completing your order.

**Use of Cookies**

We use "cookies" on this website and with the FreedomVoice mobile application. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a website visitor's hard drive or the FreedomVoice mobile application user’s device to help us improve your access to our website and identify repeat visitors. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our website. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any of your personally identifiable information.

_If you feel that we are not abiding by this policy, you should contact us immediately via phone at 800-477-1477 ext. 2 or via email at  _[ _customercare@freedomvoice.com_](mailto:customercare@freedomvoice.com) _._
